<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Water Heater Installation and Repair by Associated Plumbers 501-666-9483]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Water Heater Installation and Repair by Associated Plumbers 501-666-9483]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/water-heater-repair-in-little-rock/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 17:47:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/water-heater-repair-in-little-rock/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/4cfb5cec1df623730766ac2eec1cc201eb0366af.jpg" alt="" title="">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/water-heater-repair-in-little-rock/ca71a9ef-6bc8-4ce3-af98-aead74796a86/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ca71a9ef-6bc8-4ce3-af98-aead74796a86</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 16:40:25 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rinnai Tankless Water Heater]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Rinnai Tankless Water Heater</h1><p>If you want never ending hot water instantly.
Little Rock, AR |North Little Rock | Sherwood, AR | Maumelle, AR | College Station | Sweet Home, AR | | | | | |
Rinnai Tankless water heater installation and repair by Associated Plumbers 501-666-9483 Little Rock, North Little Rock, Sherwood, Maumelle, Mabelvale
Rinnai Continuum provides never-ending hot water to households 24 hours a day at the rate of up to 9.8 gallons per minute.
This unique feature allows homeowners the luxury of using multiple hot water sources at once without any loss of temperature consistency. Because Rinnai Continuum is not limited by capacity, as are typical 50 and 75 gallon tanks, today’s 70+ gallon bathtubs can be filled again and again without penalizing the other hot water needs in the home.
Homes with a Rinnai Continuum can run a washing machine, dishwasher and shower simultaneously without worrying about hot water running out at any source.
Rinnai Continuum is up to 50 percent more energy efficient than a traditional natural gas water heater and up to 70 percent more efficient than an electric water heater. Whereas 40-gallon tanks require 16 sq. ft. of floor space and usually last around 10 years, Rinnai Continuum is a compact wall mounted unit with a life expectancy of 25 years. Because the Continuum does not require a tank, the risk of tank-type water heater ruptures is eliminated. Rinnai Continuum can be set to operate at exact user-specifiable temperatures via the digital and easy-to-use control pad placed in multiple locations of a home. This is an extremely important feature in households with small children and elderly individuals to help prevent scalding accidents. Rinnai Continuum also offers flexibility in its wall-mounted locations. Should the user prefer to mount the unit indoors, it safely uses no indoor make-up air and vents directly to the atmosphere. However, a unique advantage of Rinnai Continuum is its ability to be mounted on the exterior of a house, completely removing a combustible device from the home and freeing up valuable floor-space. Additionally, the unit can be mounted in a recessed box, flush-mounted and painted or textured to match the external façade.
Unlike antiquated water tanks that constantly store and reheat water, the Rinnai shuts off automatically when the water source tap is closed, providing its users with significant energy cost savings. Whereas 40-gallon tanks require 16 sq. ft. of floor space and usually last around 10 years, the Rinnai is a compact wall mounted unit with a life expectancy of 25 years. Because the Rinnai does not require a tank, the risk of tank-type water heater ruptures is eliminated. The Rinnai can be set to operate at exact user-specifiable temperatures via the digital and easy-to-use control pad placed in multiple locations of a home. This is an extremely important feature in households with small children and elderly individuals to help prevent scalding accidents.
The Rinnai provides never-ending hot water to households 24 hours a day at the rate of up to 9.8 gallons per minute.</p><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/vahj1ThiexotieMo/e827f286cca78e425112dc1aae1a0f2e/passthrough.jpg?height=365&input=https%3A%2F%2Fs3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2Fthe-grid-img%2Fp%2Fe41ed41abb0597588b3b394bd644f2f1ac91c7c5.jpg&width=750"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/water-heater-repair-in-little-rock/rinnai-tankless-water-heater/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">90cd2cd7-2527-4721-ae40-3fe235cf80b4</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 17:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hybrid Heat Pump Water Heater]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Hybrid Heat Pump Water Heater</h1><p>The hybrid water heater is much more efficient than most any of the other water heaters on the market.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a5176e3404fc2758f62b78334bd7a407b27042b7.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/water-heater-repair-in-little-rock/f83892fe-c075-409a-ae50-44ead9aa229d/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f83892fe-c075-409a-ae50-44ead9aa229d</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 16:18:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Little Rock, AR |North Little Rock | Sherwood, AR | Maumelle, AR | College Station | Sweet Home, AR | | | | | |]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Little Rock, AR |North Little Rock | Sherwood, AR | Maumelle, AR | College Station | Sweet Home, AR | | | | | |</h1><p>Rinnai Tankless water heater installation and repair by Associated Plumbers 501-666-9483 Little Rock, North Little Rock, Sherwood, Maumelle, Mabelvale</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/water-heater-repair-in-little-rock/rinnai-continuum-tankless-water-heaters-in-pulaski-county/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8de1fced-1c6e-4721-af39-d1967a69ca33</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 21:18:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Associated
Plumbers
Inc.,
is an Arkansas Plumbing, repair, service, replacement company
located in Little
Rock, AR, Central
Arkansas and Pulaski
County.Associated
Plumbers,
Inc. will send you a
licensed plumber to
fix your plumbing problem as well as your hot water heaters
installation.Associated
Plumbers,
Inc. provides service to Little
Rock AR,North
Little Rock AR, Sherwood AR,  Maumelle AR, Roland AR, Natural Steps
AR, Sweet Home AR, Mabelvale AR, College Station AR,. 72114, 72216,
72118, 72201, 72202, 72204, 72205, 72206, 72207, 722009, 72210,
72211, 72212, 72223, 72227, 72113, 72120,To
set-up a repair service or replacement estimate, call 501-666-9483.Associated
Plumbers, Inc. Plumbing sells
and services many
brands of
plumbing fixtures, water heaters, tankless water heaters including A.O.
Smith, Rinnai, Insinkerator,  Kohler, American Standard, TOTO, Rheem,
State Water Heaters
   </p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/water-heater-repair-in-little-rock/12e4b5ea-6e69-4cdb-a225-2c8a3dc586ed/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">12e4b5ea-6e69-4cdb-a225-2c8a3dc586ed</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 18:14:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A.O.
Smith Water Heaters]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>A.O.
Smith Water Heaters</h1><p>A.O Smith water heater installation and repair by Associated Plumbers 501-666-9483 in Little Rock  North Little Rock Sherwood Maumelle Mabelvale </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/579695bf89a3c1c4faf1ffecf576c82cd6a319f1.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/water-heater-repair-in-little-rock/ao-smith-water-heaters/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f854cf9f-766e-4fdd-a959-2caadf94a728</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 19:12:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Setting
the Temperature on your Water Heater ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Setting
the Temperature on your Water Heater </h1><p>The
majority of injuries and deaths involving tap water scalds are to the
elderly and children under the age of five. The U.S. Consumer Product
Safety Commission (CPSC) urges all users to lower their water heaters
to 120 degrees Fahrenheit. In addition to preventing accidents, this
decrease in temperature will conserve energy and save money.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/0969009a2b1a951f979421efef1bb029acb109af.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/water-heater-repair-in-little-rock/setting-the-temperature-on-your-water-heater/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cd75abe5-071d-435b-9d3f-cdf174cd55ab</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 16:08:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>