<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Water Heater Installation and Repair by Associated Plumbers 501-666-9483]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Water Heater Installation and Repair by Associated Plumbers 501-666-9483]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/water-heater-repair-in-little-rock/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 19:24:55 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/water-heater-repair-in-little-rock/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/af1ff8c9-8f78-41c7-96fb-bfeca184e258.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/water-heater-repair-in-little-rock/ca71a9ef-6bc8-4ce3-af98-aead74796a86/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ca71a9ef-6bc8-4ce3-af98-aead74796a86</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 16:43:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Little
Rock, AR |North
Little Rock | Sherwood,
AR | Maumelle,
AR | College
Station | Sweet
Home, AR | |  |  |  | |]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Little
Rock, AR |North
Little Rock | Sherwood,
AR | Maumelle,
AR | College
Station | Sweet
Home, AR | |  |  |  | |</h1><p>Tankless Water Heater installation and repair by Associated Plumbers 501-666-9483 in  Little Rock North Little Rock Sherwood Maumelle Mabelvale</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/5dbaf4fc20a9f82f9f2455a6b1f61d92647e2130.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/water-heater-repair-in-little-rock/rinnai-continuum-tankless-water-heaters-in-pulaski-county/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8de1fced-1c6e-4721-af39-d1967a69ca33</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 19:24:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Associated
Plumbers
Inc.,
is an Arkansas Plumbing, repair, service, replacement company
located in Little
Rock, AR, Central
Arkansas and Pulaski
County.Associated
Plumbers,
Inc. will send you a
licensed plumber to
fix your plumbing problem as well as your hot water heaters
installation.Associated
Plumbers,
Inc. provides service to Little
Rock AR,North
Little Rock AR, Sherwood AR,  Maumelle AR, Roland AR, Natural Steps
AR, Sweet Home AR, Mabelvale AR, College Station AR,. 72114, 72216,
72118, 72201, 72202, 72204, 72205, 72206, 72207, 722009, 72210,
72211, 72212, 72223, 72227, 72113, 72120,To
set-up a repair service or replacement estimate, call 501-666-9483.Associated
Plumbers, Inc. Plumbing sells
and services many
brands of
plumbing fixtures, water heaters, tankless water heaters including A.O.
Smith, Rinnai, Insinkerator,  Kohler, American Standard, TOTO, Rheem,
State Water Heaters
   </p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/water-heater-repair-in-little-rock/12e4b5ea-6e69-4cdb-a225-2c8a3dc586ed/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">12e4b5ea-6e69-4cdb-a225-2c8a3dc586ed</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 18:14:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[About Us]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>About Us</h1><p>Associated Plumbers Inc. was founded circa 1947 as Ray and Reynolds Plumbing.  New construction was the primary focus of the firm until the 1960's when the firm went into service work and retail sales of plumbing parts and fixtures and become the largest service only Plumbing firm in the Little Rock area. The sales counter has the largest selection of rare and hard to find plumbing repair parts in this area and possibly the state. Associated Plumbers website went live on the web in September 1996. The On-Line store began selling products June 2001. In September 2002 we began using Flat rate pricing and Client Plumbing Program Plan.  Associated Plumbers Inc. has always been one of Central Arkansas's most admired plumbing firms. Concerns with the quality of its workmanship, no matter how large or small the project may be, have resulted in repeat clients for decades  Associated Plumbers Inc. are proud members of The Pulaski County Master Plumbers Association, Central Arkansas Joint Apprenticeship Training for the Plumbing Industry, Plumbing, Heating, Cooling Contractors-National Association, Arkansas Gas Association, Better Business Bureau, Clint Reynolds Plumbing was one of the founding members of the Pulaski County Master Plumbers Association and Central Arkansas Joint Apprenticeship Training For The Plumbing Industry back in the 1950's  You will also have the peace of mind knowing that we comply with all codes, licenses and laws.  Don’t fall into the trap of hiring a plumbing company that is able to offer a cheaper price because they operate without a license, don’t obtain the required permits, or carry adequate insurance. Associated Plumbers, Inc. is a licensed contractor and pulls municipal and state permits as required. Associated Plumbers, Inc. is insured for Workers Compensation and for liability insurance.   Compliance with codes and adequate insurance is important to you for liability reasons. If a worker is injured and the contractor is not insured, you can be held liable. Or, if there is an insurance claim due to a fire or an accident that is related to unlicensed work or work for which no permit was obtained, your insurance company may dispute the claim. You also want to avoid questions related to workmanship when you sell the house, which may end up costing you more than the original repair to correct.   With Associated Plumbers, Inc., you have peace of mind knowing that you are working with a company that has an established reputation and is only interested in doing the best job possible.  If you are looking for a Plumber, please call us today at 501-666-9483 or complete our Online service requests.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a1c67b93be22210c19f5e262f0bb97df939655a4.gif"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/water-heater-repair-in-little-rock/dd61a679-a87c-4fcd-8814-0ce6746dc97c/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">dd61a679-a87c-4fcd-8814-0ce6746dc97c</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 18:07:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A.O.
Smith Water Heaters]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>A.O.
Smith Water Heaters</h1><p>A.O Smith water heater installation and repair by Associated Plumbers 501-666-9483 in Little Rock  North Little Rock Sherwood Maumelle Mabelvale </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/579695bf89a3c1c4faf1ffecf576c82cd6a319f1.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/water-heater-repair-in-little-rock/ao-smith-water-heaters/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f854cf9f-766e-4fdd-a959-2caadf94a728</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 19:12:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Setting
the Temperature on your Water Heater ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Setting
the Temperature on your Water Heater </h1><p>The
majority of injuries and deaths involving tap water scalds are to the
elderly and children under the age of five. The U.S. Consumer Product
Safety Commission (CPSC) urges all users to lower their water heaters
to 120 degrees Fahrenheit. In addition to preventing accidents, this
decrease in temperature will conserve energy and save money.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/water-heater-repair-in-little-rock/setting-the-temperature-on-your-water-heater/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cd75abe5-071d-435b-9d3f-cdf174cd55ab</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 18:31:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>